{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, A, S, K and directed edges F->A, A->S, F->K, F->S, A->K, S->K.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node K?", "answer": "{'A', 'F', 'S'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A', 'S', 'K'} the markov blanket of node F?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node K?\nA. {'A', 'F', 'S'}\nB. {'A'}\nC. {'A', 'F'}\nD. {'F'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "11883690", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, K, S, J and directed edges K->J, K->S, I->J, S->J, I->S.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node K?", "answer": "{'J', 'I', 'S'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'J', 'I', 'K'} the markov blanket of node S?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node S?\nA. {'J', 'I', 'K'}\nB. {'I'}\nC. {'K'}\nD. {'I', 'J'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "89774331", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, R, Z, X and directed edges R->X, R->Z, J->Z, Z->X, J->R, J->X.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node Z?", "answer": "{'X', 'J', 'R'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'X', 'J', 'R'} the markov blanket of node Z?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node X?\nA. {'R', 'J'}\nB. {'R', 'Z', 'J'}\nC. {'Z', 'J'}\nD. {'J'}", "answer": "B"}], "uid": "17802319", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, U, T, Z and directed edges C->Z, C->U, C->T.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node T?", "answer": "{'C'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'C'} the markov blanket of node Z?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node Z?\nA. {'T', 'U', 'C'}\nB. {'U'}\nC. {'T', 'U'}\nD. {'C'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "83980168", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, U, I, O and directed edges H->U, H->O, I->O, U->I.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node U?", "answer": "{'I', 'H'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'U', 'I', 'O'} the markov blanket of node H?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node I?\nA. {'U', 'H'}\nB. {'U'}\nC. {'O'}\nD. {'U', 'H', 'O'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "82456619", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, V, P, H and directed edges V->H, P->H, I->H, I->P.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node P?", "answer": "{'V', 'I', 'H'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'I', 'H', 'P'} the markov blanket of node V?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node P?\nA. {'V', 'I', 'H'}\nB. {'I', 'H'}\nC. {'V'}\nD. {'I'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "18908510", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, G, J, A and directed edges J->A, F->J, F->G, G->A, G->J, F->A.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node J?", "answer": "{'A', 'F', 'G'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A', 'F', 'J'} the markov blanket of node G?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node A?\nA. {'F', 'J', 'G'}\nB. {'J'}\nC. {'F'}\nD. {'F', 'J'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "21705565", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes T, F, I, M and directed edges T->F, T->I, F->M.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node T?", "answer": "{'F', 'I'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'T'} the markov blanket of node I?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node M?\nA. {'T'}\nB. {'T', 'F', 'I'}\nC. {'F'}\nD. {'F', 'I'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "86633571", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, W, Y, E, K and directed edges I->K, Y->K, W->K, I->W, I->Y, Y->E.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node W?", "answer": "{'Y', 'I', 'K'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Y', 'I', 'W'} the markov blanket of node K?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node I?\nA. {'W', 'Y', 'K'}\nB. {'E', 'W'}\nC. {'E', 'W', 'K', 'Y'}\nD. {'W'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "33021589", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, A, M, B, I and directed edges M->I, A->M, M->B, W->A, B->I, A->I, W->I, W->M, A->B, W->B.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node W?", "answer": "{'A', 'M', 'B', 'I'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A', 'I', 'B'} the markov blanket of node M?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node I?\nA. {'A', 'W', 'M'}\nB. {'W'}\nC. {'A', 'W', 'M', 'B'}\nD. {'A', 'W'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "47486391", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, K, Y, J, W and directed edges N->Y, K->Y, K->J, N->W, Y->W, J->W, K->W, N->K, N->J, Y->J.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node J?", "answer": "{'W', 'N', 'K', 'Y'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'J', 'N', 'K'} the markov blanket of node Y?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node J?\nA. {'W', 'N', 'K', 'Y'}\nB. {'W', 'K'}\nC. {'W'}\nD. {'W', 'N', 'K'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "78766089", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, Q, F, V, T and directed edges E->T, Q->V, E->V, Q->T, E->F, V->T, F->V, Q->F.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node T?", "answer": "{'E', 'Q', 'V'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'T', 'F', 'V', 'Q'} the markov blanket of node E?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node V?\nA. {'T'}\nB. {'F'}\nC. {'E'}\nD. {'T', 'F', 'E', 'Q'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "34574183", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, Y, B, R, X and directed edges I->X, Y->R, I->R, I->Y, R->X, Y->X, B->R, I->B, B->X, Y->B.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node I?", "answer": "{'B', 'R', 'X', 'Y'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Y', 'I', 'B'} the markov blanket of node X?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node X?\nA. {'I', 'B'}\nB. {'R', 'B'}\nC. {'I'}\nD. {'R', 'Y', 'I', 'B'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "34406022", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Y, R, D, V, F and directed edges D->F, Y->D, Y->R, V->F, D->V, Y->V, R->F.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node V?", "answer": "{'F', 'R', 'Y', 'D'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'F', 'V', 'Y', 'D'} the markov blanket of node R?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node D?\nA. {'Y', 'F', 'V'}\nB. {'F', 'V', 'R', 'Y'}\nC. {'F'}\nD. {'R', 'F', 'V'}", "answer": "B"}], "uid": "84338160", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, Y, P, E, F and directed edges E->F, Y->P, K->Y, P->E, Y->E.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node F?", "answer": "{'E'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Y'} the markov blanket of node K?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node K?\nA. {'E', 'F', 'P'}\nB. {'Y', 'E'}\nC. {'E', 'F', 'Y', 'P'}\nD. {'Y'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "99968158", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, B, X, P, Z and directed edges X->Z, B->P, O->Z, B->Z.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node Z?", "answer": "{'X', 'B', 'O'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'X', 'Z', 'B', 'P'} the markov blanket of node O?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node B?\nA. {'O'}\nB. {'P'}\nC. {'Z', 'P'}\nD. {'X', 'O', 'Z', 'P'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "51877773", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, L, Q, O, X, A and directed edges L->O, L->Q, O->A, S->A, S->O, O->X, S->Q, Q->X, S->L.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node A?", "answer": "{'S', 'O'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'X', 'A', 'L', 'S', 'Q'} the markov blanket of node O?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node X?\nA. {'A', 'L', 'S', 'O', 'Q'}\nB. {'A', 'Q'}\nC. {'L'}\nD. {'Q', 'O'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "53541933", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, H, A, D, C, S and directed edges H->D, D->C, A->C, H->S, F->H, H->A, A->S, D->S, F->D.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node C?", "answer": "{'A', 'D'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A', 'D', 'H', 'S'} the markov blanket of node C?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node A?\nA. {'D', 'S', 'C'}\nB. {'S'}\nC. {'F', 'D', 'H', 'S', 'C'}\nD. {'C', 'D', 'H', 'S'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "73670900", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, A, Z, I, H, R and directed edges A->I, H->R, V->A, V->H, I->R, V->R, Z->H.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node H?", "answer": "{'V', 'R', 'Z', 'I'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'I', 'H', 'V'} the markov blanket of node R?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node V?\nA. {'Z', 'I', 'H', 'A'}\nB. {'R'}\nC. {'A', 'R', 'Z', 'I', 'H'}\nD. {'R', 'A', 'Z'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "53895338", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, K, A, H, P, E and directed edges P->E, A->P, K->P, H->P, K->E, S->A, S->K, A->E.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node S?", "answer": "{'A', 'K'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A', 'H', 'P', 'K', 'E'} the markov blanket of node S?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node H?\nA. {'S'}\nB. {'S', 'P'}\nC. {'A', 'K', 'P'}\nD. {'A', 'S', 'E', 'P'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "16664458", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, U, P, W, V, Q and directed edges U->W, U->V, U->P, P->Q, U->Q, K->W, W->Q, P->W.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node P?", "answer": "{'U', 'W', 'K', 'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Q', 'W', 'K', 'V'} the markov blanket of node P?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node U?\nA. {'W', 'P', 'K'}\nB. {'W', 'V', 'P', 'K', 'Q'}\nC. {'Q', 'W', 'P', 'V'}\nD. {'W', 'P', 'K', 'V'}", "answer": "B"}], "uid": "31191527", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, Z, H, L, U, O and directed edges N->O, Z->H, N->U, N->Z, H->O, U->O, L->U, N->L, L->O.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node N?", "answer": "{'L', 'H', 'U', 'O', 'Z'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Z', 'N', 'O'} the markov blanket of node L?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node H?\nA. {'L', 'N'}\nB. {'N'}\nC. {'L', 'Z', 'O'}\nD. {'U', 'O', 'Z', 'L', 'N'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "20284848", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, F, G, L, P, D and directed edges X->G, F->L, G->D, L->D, X->P, X->L, F->P, F->D.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node D?", "answer": "{'L', 'F', 'G'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'L', 'F', 'G'} the markov blanket of node D?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node L?\nA. {'X', 'F', 'D', 'G'}\nB. {'G', 'D', 'P'}\nC. {'X', 'G', 'D', 'P'}\nD. {'X', 'G'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "73718963", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, Q, P, J, G, D and directed edges Q->P, Z->Q, G->D, Q->D, Z->G, Z->J, Z->P, Q->J.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node J?", "answer": "{'Z', 'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Z', 'D', 'Q'} the markov blanket of node P?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node P?\nA. {'G'}\nB. {'G', 'D', 'Z', 'Q'}\nC. {'Z', 'Q'}\nD. {'Z', 'J'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "06482027", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, G, L, W, K, Y, J and directed edges G->W, W->Y, L->W, G->K, Y->J, G->J, C->J, C->L, C->Y.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node Y?", "answer": "{'W', 'J', 'C', 'G'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'L', 'Y', 'G'} the markov blanket of node C?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node K?\nA. {'W', 'J', 'G', 'C', 'Y'}\nB. {'G'}\nC. {'C'}\nD. {'L', 'J', 'Y'}", "answer": "B"}], "uid": "99060047", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, K, N, J, S, H, G and directed edges H->G, P->N, K->S, J->S, N->J, N->H, N->G.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node S?", "answer": "{'J', 'K'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'H', 'N'} the markov blanket of node G?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node J?\nA. {'N', 'S', 'K'}\nB. {'N', 'S', 'P'}\nC. {'H', 'N', 'P', 'S', 'G'}\nD. {'N', 'H', 'S', 'K'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "04719956", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, V, B, J, Q, K, U and directed edges V->Q, X->K, J->Q, X->Q, B->J, X->V, V->U, J->U, J->K.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node V?", "answer": "{'X', 'U', 'J', 'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'U', 'Q', 'V'} the markov blanket of node X?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node V?\nA. {'B', 'J', 'Q'}\nB. {'X', 'Q', 'B'}\nC. {'U', 'B', 'K', 'Q'}\nD. {'X', 'U', 'J', 'Q'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "39989152", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, V, U, J, Q, Y, I and directed edges J->Q, V->U, Y->I, V->Q, Q->Y, B->V.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node I?", "answer": "{'Y'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Y'} the markov blanket of node I?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node B?\nA. {'V'}\nB. {'J', 'Q'}\nC. {'U', 'J', 'V'}\nD. {'U', 'Q', 'V'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "65255135", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes T, J, C, K, H, E, O and directed edges T->C, K->O, J->O, E->O, J->H, K->E, C->E, C->K, J->K, T->K.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node J?", "answer": "{'T', 'H', 'C', 'K', 'O', 'E'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'T', 'E', 'C'} the markov blanket of node K?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node K?\nA. {'T', 'J', 'C', 'E', 'O'}\nB. {'E', 'T', 'H', 'C'}\nC. {'E', 'J', 'H'}\nD. {'T', 'J', 'H', 'O', 'E'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "73343110", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes T, V, H, O, X, W, B and directed edges T->W, T->V, O->W, V->O, W->B, H->W, V->X, T->X, H->B, T->H.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node B?", "answer": "{'W', 'H'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'X', 'W', 'V', 'O'} the markov blanket of node H?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node O?\nA. {'W', 'H', 'V'}\nB. {'W'}\nC. {'T', 'W', 'V', 'H'}\nD. {'T', 'H', 'V'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "32592752", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Q, N, C, B, T, F, R and directed edges Q->R, F->R, B->F, N->C, Q->T, C->T.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node R?", "answer": "{'F', 'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'F', 'Q'} the markov blanket of node R?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node Q?\nA. {'R', 'C'}\nB. {'F', 'C'}\nC. {'T', 'F', 'C', 'R'}\nD. {'N', 'B', 'C'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "16401097", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, W, N, M, Q, Y, G and directed edges W->N, Y->G, K->N, M->G, Q->G, K->Q, W->Q, M->Y.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node M?", "answer": "{'Y', 'Q', 'G'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'N', 'K', 'Q'} the markov blanket of node W?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node G?\nA. {'W', 'N', 'K', 'Y', 'Q'}\nB. {'M', 'N', 'Q'}\nC. {'Y', 'M', 'Q'}\nD. {'Y', 'Q', 'M', 'K'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "22704706", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, O, P, G, U, C, S, I and directed edges C->S, P->C, O->C, G->I, O->U, A->S, O->I.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node A?", "answer": "{'S', 'C'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'I', 'S', 'O'} the markov blanket of node C?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node G?\nA. {'A', 'S', 'C', 'U', 'O'}\nB. {'I', 'O'}\nC. {'U', 'O'}\nD. {'A', 'I', 'P', 'C', 'O'}", "answer": "B"}], "uid": "30923400", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, P, K, S, D, F, E, Q and directed edges K->Q, P->F, I->F, K->E, E->Q, P->S, K->F, K->D, D->E, S->E.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node I?", "answer": "{'F', 'P', 'K'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'F', 'P', 'K'} the markov blanket of node I?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node K?\nA. {'F', 'E', 'I', 'P'}\nB. {'E', 'D'}\nC. {'D', 'Q'}\nD. {'F', 'D', 'I', 'S', 'P', 'E', 'Q'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "97886117", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, I, N, J, C, S, Y, W and directed edges N->Y, I->J, X->N, C->W, I->C, N->C, X->C, I->S, C->Y, S->W.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node X?", "answer": "{'C', 'I', 'N'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'W', 'N', 'S', 'X', 'C'} the markov blanket of node I?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node I?\nA. {'Y', 'W', 'N', 'C'}\nB. {'W', 'N', 'S'}\nC. {'X', 'J', 'C', 'N', 'S'}\nD. {'W', 'N', 'S', 'C', 'Y'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "90267949", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, C, M, V, Y, G, K, A and directed edges V->K, P->Y, C->A, M->V, K->A, M->Y, Y->A, V->G, M->G, P->C.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node P?", "answer": "{'Y', 'M', 'C'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A', 'M', 'G', 'C', 'Y'} the markov blanket of node K?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node C?\nA. {'A', 'M', 'V', 'P', 'Y'}\nB. {'M', 'K', 'P'}\nC. {'A', 'Y', 'K', 'P'}\nD. {'A', 'V', 'G', 'P', 'Y'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "46582375", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, T, V, U, Y, K, Q, X and directed edges V->K, T->X, O->Q, Y->K, O->T, O->U, U->K, V->Y, K->X.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node O?", "answer": "{'T', 'U', 'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'V', 'O', 'Y', 'K'} the markov blanket of node U?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node Y?\nA. {'U', 'V', 'K'}\nB. {'X', 'Q'}\nC. {'K', 'O'}\nD. {'X'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "48825255", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, C, H, P, R, M, Q, F and directed edges X->P, R->M, C->F, X->C, X->R, P->F, H->Q, Q->F, P->M.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node F?", "answer": "{'Q', 'P', 'C'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'F', 'C', 'H', 'P'} the markov blanket of node Q?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node M?\nA. {'R', 'H', 'P', 'C'}\nB. {'R', 'P'}\nC. {'C'}\nD. {'Q', 'P'}", "answer": "B"}], "uid": "28362836", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes U, W, E, L, K, B, D, T and directed edges E->D, L->B, W->K, W->E, U->W, B->D, K->T, W->D, W->T, U->E.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node D?", "answer": "{'E', 'W', 'B'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'W', 'B', 'D', 'K', 'E'} the markov blanket of node U?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node E?\nA. {'U', 'W', 'B', 'D'}\nB. {'T', 'W', 'B', 'L', 'D'}\nC. {'U'}\nD. {'L', 'D', 'T', 'B'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "04482730", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes S, Y, Z, W, G, X, H, N and directed edges Y->W, H->N, Y->N, Z->H, X->H, S->H, Y->G, Z->W.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node H?", "answer": "{'X', 'Y', 'Z', 'N', 'S'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'H', 'N', 'G', 'X', 'Z'} the markov blanket of node S?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node G?\nA. {'Y'}\nB. {'Y', 'W'}\nC. {'N'}\nD. {'Z', 'N', 'S'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "73224967", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, G, Q, X, F, R, P, W, Z and directed edges J->F, R->P, Q->P, R->W, Q->X, Q->Z, J->G, X->Z, G->X.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node W?", "answer": "{'R'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'X', 'W', 'J', 'G'} the markov blanket of node F?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node G?\nA. {'W', 'J', 'P', 'Q'}\nB. {'X', 'Q', 'J'}\nC. {'R', 'F', 'W'}\nD. {'F', 'R', 'X', 'Z', 'Q'}", "answer": "B"}], "uid": "78249331", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Y, E, A, P, B, L, S, K, X and directed edges Y->X, E->B, Y->P, A->S, K->X, Y->L, Y->A, B->L, A->L, P->X.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node B?", "answer": "{'A', 'Y', 'E', 'L'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'E', 'Y', 'K'} the markov blanket of node P?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node X?\nA. {'E', 'S'}\nB. {'Y', 'P', 'K'}\nC. {'E'}\nD. {'A', 'B', 'K', 'P', 'Y'}", "answer": "B"}], "uid": "28239510", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, D, Y, M, K, E, Z, I, U and directed edges K->I, F->Y, M->E, Z->I, F->E, D->K, F->I, K->U, Y->M, D->U.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node E?", "answer": "{'F', 'M'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Y', 'U', 'K'} the markov blanket of node E?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node F?\nA. {'E', 'I', 'M', 'K'}\nB. {'M', 'Z', 'Y', 'E', 'I', 'K'}\nC. {'Y', 'I', 'E'}\nD. {'Z', 'M'}", "answer": "B"}], "uid": "23776789", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, U, D, J, V, A, C, Q, P and directed edges K->V, D->Q, J->V, U->C, V->P, D->P, D->A, U->D.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node D?", "answer": "{'A', 'U', 'V', 'P', 'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A', 'J', 'D', 'K', 'P'} the markov blanket of node U?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node K?\nA. {'D', 'P'}\nB. {'Q'}\nC. {'A', 'J', 'P', 'U', 'C'}\nD. {'J', 'V'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "19709357", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, D, V, B, A, I, G, K, W and directed edges B->I, B->W, I->W, V->A, V->W, D->G, D->I, C->B, A->K.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node A?", "answer": "{'K', 'V'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'W', 'B', 'V', 'I', 'G'} the markov blanket of node A?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node D?\nA. {'A', 'I', 'W', 'G'}\nB. {'A', 'B', 'I', 'G', 'C'}\nC. {'A', 'I', 'K', 'C'}\nD. {'I', 'B', 'G'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "39290304", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, M, G, O, N, P, C, Y, Z and directed edges R->N, C->Y, R->P, G->Y, M->O, Y->Z, N->Z, M->Y.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node N?", "answer": "{'R', 'Z', 'Y'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Y', 'M', 'G'} the markov blanket of node C?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node P?\nA. {'Y', 'Z'}\nB. {'Y', 'N', 'Z', 'C'}\nC. {'Z', 'N', 'C', 'O'}\nD. {'R'}", "answer": "D"}], "uid": "78448682", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, F, N, S, L, K, Q, Z, D and directed edges L->D, K->Z, Z->D, K->D, G->Q, F->L, Q->Z, G->N, S->L.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node D?", "answer": "{'L', 'Z', 'K'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Z', 'D', 'Q', 'L'} the markov blanket of node K?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node G?\nA. {'F', 'S'}\nB. {'L', 'N'}\nC. {'N', 'Q'}\nD. {'F', 'N', 'S', 'K', 'Q'}", "answer": "C"}], "uid": "18154652", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes U, H, D, Q, E, Z, T, B, C and directed edges Q->E, U->Z, Q->T, H->T, D->E, E->B, U->H, U->C, D->Q.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "What is the markov blanket of node Q?", "answer": "{'T', 'E', 'D', 'H'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'T', 'D', 'Z'} the markov blanket of node C?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is the markov blanket of node B?\nA. {'E'}\nB. {'D', 'H', 'U', 'E', 'Q'}\nC. {'E', 'D', 'H'}\nD. {'T', 'Q'}", "answer": "A"}], "uid": "82474582", "graph_type": "DAG"}
